Guide to the Northcutt Ely Papers, 1900-1982
Department of Special Collections
- Series 5. Pamphlets
  - Before the Secretary of the Interior: brief on the Minidoka Irrigation District ....n.d., Accession no. M0252; 9 (Box 95)
  - Boulder Canyon - Colorado River Compact - Metropolitan Water District Act, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 11 (Box 95)
  - Boulder Canyon Project: to convert a natural menace into a national resource. -- Sacramento, Calif.: California State Printing Office, 1930, Accession no. M0252; 16 (Box 95)
  - Care and use of oil country tubular goods: API code of recommended field practice. -- [S.l.]: American Petroleum Institute, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 18 (Box 95)
  - Carpenter, Delph E. Conflict of jurisdiction respecting control of waters in Western States, 1929 Aug., Accession no. M0252; 19 (Box 95)
  - Carpenter, Delph E. Interstate river compacts and their place in water utilization. -- Reprint from Journal of the American Water Works Assoc., Vol. 20, no. 6, 1928 Dec., Accession no. M0252; 20 (Box 95)
  - College verse, Vol. 7, no. 2. -- [S.l.]: College Poetry Society of America Publishers, 1937 Dec., Accession no. M0252; 21 (Box 95)
  - Collom, R.E. and C.P. Watson. Review of development at Kettleman Hill. -- (Technical Publications, no. 772). -- [S.l.]: American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers, 1937, Accession no. M0252; 22 (Box 95)
  - Colorado River and the Boulder Canyon Project: historical and physical facts in connection with the Colorado River and lower basin development. -- Sacramento, Calif.: California State Printing Office, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 23 (Box 95)
  - Colorado River Compact Boulder Canyon Project. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 24 (Box 95)
  - The conservation of gas: report to the Technical Sub-Committee of the American Petroleum Institute Gas Conservation Committee, 1927 Dec., Accession no. M0252; 25 (Box 95)
  - Cylinder gates and entrance liners for intake towers at Hoover Dam: invitation for bids, schedules, etc. -- [Washington, D.C.?]: U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1933, Accession no. M0252; 26 (Box 95)
  - Dean, R.S., E.P. Barrett, and Calvin Pearson. Some observations on sponge iron .... -- [S.l.]: American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers, 1935, Accession no. M0252; 27 (Box 95)
  - Federal Oil Conservation Board: surveys of national petroleum requirements for seaonal periods of 1932-1931-1930. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 34 (Box 95)
  - Grazing on public domain: hearings before the Committee on the Public Lands, House of Representatives, 72nd Congress, 1st session on H.R. 11816. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 35 (Box 95)
  - A guide to the exhibition of historical medals in the British Museum. -- London: Oxford University Press, 1924, Accession no. M0252; 42 (Box 95)
  - Handbook on unitization of oil pools. -- [S.l.]: Mid-continent Oil and Gas Assoc., 1930, Accession no. M0252; 44 (Box 95)
  - Hoover Dam project and present status, 1931 Dec., Accession no. M0252; 47 (Box 95)
  - Mead, Elwood and Raymond F. Walter. Boulder Dam today. -- Reprint from Engineering News-Record, 1930 Feb. 6, Accession no. M0252; 52 (Box 95)
  - Measuring, sampling, and testing crude oil API code. -- [S.l.]: American Petroleum Institute, 1930 and 1931, Accession no. M0252; 53; 1 pamphlet (Box 95)
  - Message of the President of the United States communicated to the two houses of Congress, Dec. 9, 1932, 2nd session of 72nd Congress. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 54 (Box 95)
  - Oil land leasing act of 1920. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1936, Accession no. M0252; 55 (Box 95)
  - Oil shale lands: hearings before the Committee on Public Lands and Survey, United States Senate, 71st Congress, 3rd session on S. Res. 379. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 56 (Box 95)
  - O'Shaughnessy, Michael. Oil tariff and world zoning. -- New York: South American Oil Reports, Inc., 1931, Accession no. M0252; 57 (Box 95)
  - Plan, cost analysis and agreement covering consolidation and unit operation of Kern Front oil field,n.d., Accession no. M0252; 58 (Box 95)
  - Proceedings of the National Park Conference. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1915, Accession no. M0252; 61 (Box 95)
  - Report to House of Representatives on crude petroleum and its liquid refined products. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 62 (Box 95)
  - Revenue revision 1932: hearings before the Committee on Ways and Means, House of Representatives, 72nd Congress, 1st session. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 63 (Box 95)
  - Sahlin, Carl. Svenskt Stal. -- Stockholm: [s.n.], 1931, Accession no. M0252; 64 (Box 95)
  - Second deficiency appropriation bill for 1930: hearing before the Sub-committee of House Committee on Appropriations, 71st Congress, 2nd session on H.R. 12902. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1930, Accession no. M0252; 66; 4 vol. (Box 95)
  - Speiser, E.A. Ethnic movements in the Near East in the 2nd millenium B.C. -- [S.l.]: J.H. Furst, Co., 1933, Accession no. M0252; 67 (Box 95)
  - Stanley, James G. The drama of the oil industry: calling for federal regulations. -- New York: [s.n.], n.d., Accession no. M0252; 68 (Box 95)
  - Stone Age antiquities. -- London: Oxford University Press, 1926, Accession no. M0252; 69 (Box 95)
  - The story of the Hoover Dam, Vol. 1 & 2. -- [S.l.]: Ingersoll-Rand Co., 1932 July, Accession no. M0252; 70 (Box 95)
  - The story of Steuben Glass. -- New York: [s.n.], n.d., Accession no. M0252; 71 (Box 95)
  - Summarized record of meeting held by the Technical Sub-committee of the American Petroleum Institute Gas Conservation Committee, 1927, Accession no. M0252; 72 (Box 95)
  - Taylor, Katherine Ames. The story of Stanford. -- San Francisco, Calif.: H.S. Crocker Co., Inc., 1935, Accession no. M0252; 73 (Box 95)
  - Treasures of Carniola: unique collection of prehistoric antiquities...: auction catalog. -- New York: American Art Assoc., Anderson Galleries, Inc., 1934, Accession no. M0252; 74 (Box 95)
  - U.S. construction railroad Hoover Dam. -- [Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 75 (Box 95)
  - U.S. mining laws circular no. 430. -- [Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1922 Apr. 11, Accession no. M0252; 76 (Box 95)
  - West, Louis C. Roman Britain: the objects of trade. -- Oxford: Basil Blackwell, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 77 (Box 95)
  - Wheeler Williams. -- (American sculptor series). -- New York: W.W. Norton & Co., 1947, Accession no. M0252; 78 (Box 95)
  - Wu, Yuan-li. Strategic significance of Singapore. -- Washington, D.C.: American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1972, Accession no. M0252; 79 (Box 95)
  - Zimmer, George Frederick. The use of meteoric iron by primitive man. -- London: [s.n.], 1916, Accession no. M0252; 80 (Box 95)
  - Lechler, George. The Viking finds from Beardmore, Ontario. -- Reprint from the Art Quarterly, 1939 Spring, Accession no. M0252; 50 (Box 96)
  - Portraits en Medaille. -- Paris: Encyclopedie Alpina Ilustrees, 1946, Accession no. M0252; 60 (Box 96)
  - Applications for patent on oil-shale lands: hearings before the Committee on the Public Lands, House of Representatives, 71st Congress, 2nd session on H.R. 3754, H.R. 12802, and H.R. 13191. Parts 2. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1930, Accession no. M0252; 3; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Boulder Canyon Project: all-American canal. -- [S.l.]: United States Dept. of the Interior, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 12; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Boulder Canyon Project: contract for delivery of water. -- [S.l.]: United States Dept. of the Interior, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 13; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Boulder Canyon Project: contract for electrical energy. -- [S.l.]: United States Dept. of the Interior, 1920, Accession no. M0252; 14; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Collom, R.E. and C.P. Watson. Review of development at Kettleman Hill. -- (Technical Publications, no. 772). -- [S.l.]: American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers, 1937, Accession no. M0252; 22; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Colorado River Compact Boulder Canyon Project. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 24; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Ely, Northcutt. The conservation of oil. -- Cambridge, Mass.: Harvard Law Review Assoc., 1938, Accession no. M0252; 30; 12 duplicates (Box 97)
  - Ely, Northcutt. Governmental regulations of oil production, 1937, Accession no. M0252; 29; 4 duplicates (Box 97)
  - Federal Oil Conservation Board: surveys of national petroleum requirements for seaonal periods of 1932-1931-1930. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 34; 3 duplicates (Box 97)
  - Mead, Elwood and Raymond F. Walter. Boulder Dam today. -- Reprint from Engineering News-Record, 1930 Feb. 6, Accession no. M0252; 52; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - U.S. mining laws circular no. 430. -- [Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1922 Apr. 11, Accession no. M0252; 76; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - The natural gas supply and its conservation / by Claude C. Brown, Railroad Commissioner of the State of California. -- San Francisco, Calif.: [s.n.], 1930 Sept. 9, Accession no. M0252; 31 p. (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Background of voluntary and official efforts to stabilize the oil industry / Texas Oil States National. -- [S.l.]: Texas Senate Committee to Study Oil, Gas, and Mineral, 1931 Apr. 15, Accession no. M0252; 50 p. (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Extracts from the Annual report of the Secretary of the Interior / Ray Lyman Wilbur,1931 June 30, Accession no. M0252; 5 p. (2 copies) (Box 98, Folder 2)
    On the subject of oil and gas
  - A comparative analysis of the present oil and gas conservation laws of principal oil states, n.d., Accession no. M0252; 40 p. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - The petroleum industry: an address before the American Petroleum Institute / by Robert T. Lamont, Secretary of Commerce. -- Chicago, Ill.: The Institute, 1931 Nov. 11, Accession no. M0252; 10 p. (2 copies) (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - An act for the conservation of oil and gas and protection of American sources thereof from injury, authorizing an interstate compact, authorizing the Tariff Committee to make investigations and determinations with respect to oil and products thereof, and authorizing the Secretary of the Treasury to enforce said Commission's determinations with respect to importations, 1932 Jan. 27, Accession no. M0252; 6 p. (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Secretary of the Interior. TLS to Hon. George W. Norris, Chairman, Committee on Judiciary, U.S. Senate re: bill S. 4624,1932 Mar. 13, Accession no. M0252; 4 p. (2 copies) (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - The interdependence of the states in oil conservation: a survey of the interstate compact plan / by Northcutt Ely, 1932 Sept. 30, Accession no. M0252; 22 p., plus annotations (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Series 6. Reports
  - Annual report of the Department of the Interior, 1929. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 1 (Box 90)
  - Annual report of the Department of the Interior, 1930. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1930, Accession no. M0252; 2 (Box 90)
  - Annual report of the Department of the Interior, 1931. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 3 (Box 90)
  - Annual report of the Director of the National Park Service, 1932. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 4 (Box 90)
  - Annual report of the Secretary of the Interior. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1928, Accession no. M0252; 5 (Box 90)
  - Annual report of the Secretary of the Interior. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 6 (Box 90)
  - Annual report of the Secretary of the Interior. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1930, Accession no. M0252; 7 (Box 90)
  - Annual report of the Secretary of the Interior. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 7b (Box 90)
  - Ninth annual report of the Federal Power Commission. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 10 (Box 91)
  - Official register of the U.S., 1932. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 12 (Box 92)
  - Water Resources Law. Report of the President's Water Resource Policy Commission, Vol. 3, Accession no. M0252 (Box 92)
  - Hoover Institution Press. Yearbook on international affairs, 1968, Accession no. M0252 (Box 93)
  - Hoover Institution Press. Yearbook on international affairs, 1970, Accession no. M0252 (Box 93)
  - Hoover Institution Press. Yearbook on international affairs, 1971, Accession no. M0252 (Box 93)
  - Hoover Institution Press. Yearbook on international affairs, 1972, Accession no. M0252 (Box 93)
  - Ninth annual report of the Federal Power Commission. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 11 (Box 94)
  - Report five of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States, 1932. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 16 (Box 94)
  - Report IV of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States, 1932. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1930, Accession no. M0252; 17 (Box 94)
  - Bailey, Paul. Summary report on the water resources of California and a coordinated plan for their development. -- Sacramento: California State Printing Office, 1927, Accession no. M0252; 8 (Box 95)
  - Bailey, Paul. Supplementary report on water resources of California. -- Sacramento: California State Printing Office, 1925, Accession no. M0252; 9 (Box 95)
  - Report of the California Joint Federal-State Water Resources Commission to the President of the United States and Governor of the State of California. -- Sacramento: California State Printing Office, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 13 (Box 95)
  - Report of the Colorado River Board on the Boulder Dam project. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1928, Accession no. M0252; 14 (Box 95)
  - Report of the Committee on the Conservation and Administration of the Public Domain. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 15 (Box 95)
  - Report III of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 18 (Box 95)
  - Report II of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States, Jan. 1928. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1928, Accession no. M0252; 19 (Box 95)
  - Galloway, George P. Editorial Research Reports: control of production in oil industry, 1931, Accession no. M0252; 20 (Box 95)
  - Memorial address delivered before the two houses of Congress on the life and character of A. Lincoln, J. Garfield, William McKinley / by C.R. Cushman. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1903, Accession no. M0252 (Box 95, Folder 100)
  - Supreme Court #477 petition by Northcutt Ely, Accession no. M0252 (Box 95, Folder 101)
  - American maritime cases, 1933, Accession no. M0252 (Box 95, Folder 102)
  - U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals #8510, Accession no. M0252; 4 vol. (Box 95, Folder 103)
  - Central Arizona project: hearings before the Sub-committee on Irrigation and Reclamation, 1949, Accession no. M0252 (Box 96, Folder 100)
  - Ninth annual report of the Federal Power Commission. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 10; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Report five of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States, 1932. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1932, Accession no. M0252; 16; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Report IV of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States, 1932. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1930, Accession no. M0252; 17; 3 duplicates (Box 97)
  - Report III of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1929, Accession no. M0252; 18; 3 duplicates (Box 97)
  - Report II of the Federal Oil Conservation Board to the President of the United States, Jan. 1928. -- Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1928, Accession no. M0252; 19; 1 duplicate (Box 97)
  - Operating regulations to govern the production of oil and gas / Dept. of the Interior. U.S. Geological Survey. -- rev. and approved, 1926 July 1, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Tentative draft of Uniform Legislative Act for conservations and interstate compact: submitted at Austin, Texas, Conference of Committee / Legal Sub-committee of Oil States Advisory Committee, 1931 May 4, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Vacant public lands on July 1, 1931. -- (Circular, no. 1258). -- Washington, D.C.: Dept. of the Interior. General Land Office, 1931 July 1, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Some influence of foreign demand on the domestic oil situation / by E.B. Swanson. -- New York: [s.n.], 1932 Feb., Accession no. M0252; 2 copies (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Protection of the Palo Verde Valley, Calif.: H.R. Report, no. 587, 72nd Congress, 1932 Feb. 20, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - A bill for the conservation of oil and gas and protection of American sources thereof from injury, correlation of domestic and foreign production, and consenting to an interstate compact for such purposes: H.R. 12076, 1932 May 14, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Series 7. Miscellaneous
  - Subseries 1. Veterans of Foreign Wars and Their Dependents
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman. TLS to Northcutt Ely re: veteran's matters, 1929 May 24, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, John H. Memorandum on government activities for relief of war veterans, 1929 July 24, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, John H. Memorandum relating to legislation for better coordination of government activities dealing with veterans, 1929 June 26, Accession no. M0252; 15 p. (2 copies) (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Ely, Northcutt. Memorandum of suggestions for preliminary steps in coordination of veteran's relief organizations of the government, 1929 Aug. 19, Accession no. M0252; (2 copies) (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary report to the President from the Committee of Coordination of Veteran's matters,1929 Oct. 1, Accession no. M0252; 3 p. (2 copies) (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - A bill to authorize the President to consolidate and coordinate governmental activities affecting war veterans, pensioners, and civilian employees, n.d., Accession no. M0252; 4 p. (2 copies) (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2. Miscellaneous reports, briefs, memoranda of Congressional matters
    - Sibert report no. 1: report of the Colorado River Board on the Boulder Dam project. -- Document H.R. no. 446, 1928 Dec. 3, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Reply brief of California: State of Arizona vs. States of California, Nevada, Utah, New Mexico, Colorado, Wyoming and Ray Lyman Wilbur, Secretary of the Interior, in the Supreme Court of the United States, 1930 Oct., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Contract for construction of Hoover Dam, Power Plant and Appurtenant Works, 1931 Mar. 11, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of the Interior. Memorandum for the press release re: economics in the Dept. of the Interior, 1932 Mar. 9, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - A memorandum to the Secretary of the Interior summarizing Indian irrigation activities with recommendations / by Charles A. Dobbel, [1931] Dec. 16, Accession no. M0252; 30 p. (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Unit development contract, Pitchfork structure, Park County, Wyoming, 1932 Jan. 1, Accession no. M0252; 9 p. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Criticism by Walter Boards' attorney, H.L. Carnahan on the All-American Canal Project by Dr. S.S.M. Jennings,1932 June 9, Accession no. M0252; 14 p. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Memorandum re: interstate agreements of compacts within the purview of Article I, Section 10, of the Constitution, n.d., Accession no. M0252; 39 p. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - The Journal of the Society of Architectural Historians, Vol. 8, nos. 1-2, 1949 Jan. - June, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 3. Early iron castings of personal importance
    - Subsubseries 1. Published information
      - Presidential address / by Professor Henry Louis of the Iron and Steel Institute, 1929 May, Accession no. M0252; 12 p. (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Iron in antiquity / by T.A. Rickard of the Iron and Steel Institute, 1929 Sept., Accession no. M0252; 18 p. (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Composition and microstructure of ancient iron castings / by Maurice L. Pinel, Thomas T. Reed, Thomas A. Wright. -- (Technical publication, no. 882). -- American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers, 1938 Feb., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Casts: listing of objects in the collection of the Walters Art Gallery, n.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Geographical Review. -- New York: American Geographical Society of New York, 1934 Oct., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Subsubseries 2. Correspondence, Transcripts
      - Republic Steel Corp. TL to Mr. W.A. Havens, Vice President, Arthur G. McKee Co., 1933 Sept. 2, Accession no. M0252; photocopy (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - [Republic Steel Corp.] TL to Mr. Earl Smith, [193?] Aug. 15, Accession no. M0252; photocopy (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Boak, A.E.R. TLS to H.C. Richardson, 1939 May 18, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Richardson, H.C. TL to A.E.R. Boak, 1939 May 26, Accession no. M0252; photocopy (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Richardson, H.C. TL to A.E.R. Boak, 1942 Jan. 9, Accession no. M0252; photocopy (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Richardson, H.C. TL to A.E.R. Boak, 1942 Jan. 16, Accession no. M0252; photocopy (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Boak, A.E.R. TLS to H.C. Richardson, 1942 Jan. 14, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Subsubseries 3. Hand-written notes
      - Iron Age, with Prehistoric and primitive iron smelting by E. Wyndham Hulme, B.A.. -- Reprinted from Engineering, 1938 June 3, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Chalybian iron, with The Chalybes: reference listn.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Damascus steeln.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Greek minesn.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Greek ironn.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Macedonian.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Pick-upsn.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Spartan.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Untitled notesn.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Subsubseries 4. Miscellaneous
      - Letter to Alumni and friends of Stanford University from University President Ray Lyman Wilbur, 1927 May 6, Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - A university to be / by Prof. H.W. Wolfe. -- Reprint from Stanford Sequian.d., Accession no. M0252 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Series 8. Oil and Gas files
  - 0 - Imports - H.R. 10362, 108631932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Re: legislative bills H,R. 10862, 10863, 12076. Correspondence, bills, reports, hearings, drafts. Correspondents, etc.: Ray Lyman Wilbur; George W. Norris.